Look, it's the sea.
哇 是海耶
Such a vast sea.
好廣闊的大海
It's especially refreshing under nature,
在大自然之中就是格外涼快
and you can even smell the sea breeze.
還聞得到海風的味道
When the sea breeze is strong, the humidity is high,
海風大的時候會帶有鹽分
making hair care difficult.
護髮會變得有點麻煩
Is that so?
原來如此
Is it really okay for you to come out today?
不過 妳今天真的方便嗎
No problem, because today is a "special outing".
嗯 因為今天是一趟特別之旅
Indeed, it is.
的確是這樣沒錯
You're using the handkerchief I gave you.
你用了我送你的手帕耶
Of course.
那當然了
After all, this is a gift from you.
這可是妳送我的禮物啊
I'm glad you like it.
你喜歡就好
I chose it based on how I perceived you.
我是依照你給我的印象選的
Oh, I see.
這樣啊...
(The College Girl is Really Impressive) What should I write for this year's book recommendation?
(女大生真不得了) 今年的推薦書籍該選哪本好呢
STAFF PICKS: THIS YEAR'S BOOK RECOMMENDATION Hello, Mr. Sajo.
(店員精選 今年首推書籍) 佐城先生你好
Welcome, Miss Sasaki. Are you heading to campus today?
歡迎光臨 笹木小姐 妳今天是準備要去學校嗎
No, I'm planning to go to the library.
不是的 我打算去一趟圖書館
I had something to tell you, so I came here.
想說來找你聊個天 所以就過來了
Really?
真的嗎
Your regular visits help to heal both my body and mind.
妳常常光臨 讓我覺得很療癒
That's a stylish bracelet. So you will also wear such accessories.
好時尚的手鏈 原來妳也會戴這類的飾品啊
I just got influenced by a friend.
這是受到朋友的影響
I even made a bracelet with my father not long ago.
不久前我跟我爸一起去製作手鏈
Made it yourself?
自己手工做的嗎
Speaking of which, this college girl gets along well with her father.
這女大生跟爸爸的關係也太好了吧
Big Sis has requested separate laundry from our father since elementary school.
哪像我老姊 小學就要求衣物要跟爸爸分開洗了
Mr. Sajo?
佐城先生？
It's nothing. I just think you're so crafty.
沒事 我只是想說妳手好巧
This was made in a seaside store, where the owner taught me as I made it.
那家店靠近海邊 老闆會一邊教我們一邊製作
That's really nice.
真不錯耶
What's the name of the store?
那家店叫什麼名字
Let me see.
我看看
This is the one.
就是這家店
It's a shop run by a beautiful older sister.
是一個漂亮的大姐姐獨自經營的店鋪
I think you would definitely like it.
感覺你一定會喜歡
Do I look like I like older sisters that much?
我看起來像是喜歡大姐姐...
You would probably like this kind of personally run shop, right?
我想說你應該會喜歡這種 個人經營的店鋪吧
Yes, I quite like it.
呃 我是滿喜歡的
Do I need to take a train and a bus from here?
從這出發的話要搭電車再轉公車嗎
Are you going?
你想去嗎
Yes, because the crafts are beautiful.
嗯... 因為手工藝品很漂亮嘛
And…
而且…
And?
而且？
I can design my own accessories.
還能依個人喜好製作飾品
Natsukawa's birthday is coming up, what should I give her this year?
夏川的生日快到了 今年我要送她什麼才好
I have even considered whether or not to give her…
老實說我一直在思考到底該不該送她
Oh, they can even make such an accessory.
這種飾品也能自己做啊
What's wrong, Miss Sasaki?
笹木小姐...
Would you like to go together?
妳要跟我一起去嗎
And so, I never thought
於是 萬萬沒想到
I would go on a special outing with a college girl.
我會跟女大生一起來趟特別之旅
Is this the effortless skill of a college girl?
難道這就是女大生的游刃有餘嗎
She doesn't seem to have any special feelings
她好像對我們單獨出遊這件事
about going out with me alone.
沒有什麼特別的感覺
Miss Sasaki?
妳怎麼了嗎
Well, I was thinking about being seen by others and…
我想說要是被別人看到就...
Is it because you're shy about being misunderstood as my girlfriend?
妳是怕被別人誤會妳跟我是情侶嗎
It's because of this dress.
是因為這件衣服
Huh? The dress?
衣服？
You still give off a mature big sister vibe, as per usual.
妳跟平時一樣 就是成熟大姐姐的感覺呀
No, it's not like that.
不是那樣的...
Actually, I only wear this dress
其實這身裝扮 我只有在跟你見面時
when I see you or other people outside of campus.
或是跟學校以外的人見面時才會穿的
Huh? Then what do you usually wear?
咦 那妳平常都穿什麼呢
I usually wear the clothes I wore in elementary school.
我平常都穿...小學時的衣服
Can you still fit into your elementary school clothes?
小學的衣服竟然還穿得下
Won't your friends say anything about it?
妳的朋友沒有表示什麼意見嗎
For example, you should wear other clothes.
例如建議妳換件衣服之類的
How did you know?
你怎麼會知道
People often say that to me.
常常有人這麼對我說
Those clothes are cute and I quite like them.
那些衣服很可愛 我還滿喜歡的
Um… how should I put it?
這...該怎麼說呢
It's fine to wear them at home.
在家裡穿是還可以啦
I see.
你說的對...
But I think it is fantastic that
不過 妳這麼愛惜物品
you can keep clothes for so long.
我覺得很棒
Thank you for your compliment.
謝謝你的誇獎
AIKA, I'M HERE -I MIGHT BE A WHILE -OKAY
(小愛 我到了) (-我快到了 -好)
Kei.
圭
Sorry, I came late because I was helping Airi change clothes.
抱歉 我幫愛莉找衣服就遲到了
It's okay.
沒關係
Airi!
小愛莉
Kei, what did you pack in there?
圭 妳包包裡裝了什麼
We need to pack a lot for the beach, right? What'd you pack?
去海邊當然要準備很多東西啊 小愛妳不也裝了不少
More than half of the items are Airi's.
有一半都是愛莉的東西...
This is the Sajo house, isn't it?
這是小佐城家吧
Sajo really lucked out.
小佐城真是走運
He gets to see you in a swimsuit.
居然可以看到小愛穿泳裝的樣子
Should we call him?
妳也要約他嗎
Let's give him the heavy duty of carrying the luggage.
我們就把提行李的重任交給他吧
But, all of a sudden, I am not sure he would agree.
但這麼突然 他會答應嗎
Huh? He went out to work?
咦 他去打工了嗎
I thought he must be idle.
我還以為他一定閒著沒事
Going to the beach with Kei!
我要跟圭姐姐一起去海邊
Going to the beach! Airi, come here!
小愛莉走吧 去海邊囉
Because of the beautiful white coastline, everyone says it is called White Beach.
這裡因為有美麗的白色海濱 難怪叫做“美白濱”
Yeah.
是啊
Do college girls usually go for drives on dates?
女大生平常約會時 是不是會開車兜風之類的呢
Are you looking for a beautiful big sister in a swimsuit? You can't do that.
你該不會是在尋找泳裝美女吧 這樣不行哦
I-I would never do something like that.
我怎麼會做這種事呢
I'm just marveling at how beautiful the sea is.
我只是在感慨海景原來這麼美
Mr. Sajo, you said you haven't been to the beach for a while, right?
你說你很久沒來海邊了吧
It's been a few years since I've been.
我好幾年沒來了
Do you often come to the beach, Miss Sasaki?
笹木小姐妳常來海邊嗎
Yes, I came with my family last year. Though I haven't gone swimming this year.
是的 我去年也跟家人來過 但今年還沒下水游泳
I came here with my friends when I was in middle school.
我大概就是國中時跟朋友去的吧
I'm about the same.
我也差不多是這樣
It's troublesome to buy a new swimsuit every year, isn't it?
每年都得買新泳裝也很麻煩
Huh? Don't you wear last year's?
咦 妳不穿去年的泳裝嗎
It doesn't fit anymore.
想必是穿不下吧...
Mr. Sajo?
佐城先生？
Let's see. Where do we go from here?
接下來要往哪走...
Over there. I remember the way, let me lead.
往那邊走 我還記得路 所以讓我來帶路吧
Really?
真的嗎
Then I'll leave it to you.
那就拜託妳...
T-This is impure interaction between the sexes!
這...這是不健全的異性交往
M-Miss Sasaki.
笹...笹木小姐
I'm sorry! I accidentally and habitually… I'm really sorry.
對不起 我不是故意的... 很抱歉
It's okay, no need to apologize.
沒關係 妳不必道歉
Anyway, let's go.
總之 我們走吧
Okay.
好
Are your feet alright?
妳的腳沒事吧
They're fine because the soles of the shoes are thick.
沒事 鞋底很厚
Let's walk slowly then.
我們慢慢走過去吧
Thank you.
謝謝你
Okay.
好
The college girl is really impressive.
女大生真是不得了
Is it here? I suddenly feel a bit nervous.
就是這裡嗎 我突然有點緊張了起來
No need to be nervous.
不用緊張
I've been here before. Let's go in.
我之前來過 我們進去吧
Oh, okay.
喔 好的
I'm the only guy?
就我一個男的嗎
Now I'm getting even more nervous.
這下我更緊張了
Welcome.
歡迎光臨
Oh? You are…
妳是...
Hello, I've been here before.
妳好 我之前也來過
I knew it. There was a mature girl left a lasting impression on me.
果然是妳 我就對妳這個成熟的女孩很有印象
Is it?
會嗎
Are you here with your boyfriend today?
妳今天跟男朋友一起來嗎
Uh, well, he is…
呃...他是...
We're not in that kind of relationship.
我們不是那種關係
Oh, is that so?
哎呀 是嗎
-What's this? -Take your time to look.
-這是怎樣 -你們慢慢看吧
-White-collar beauty and college girl love topic? -Okay.
-白領佳人與女大生的戀愛話題 -好的
I suddenly feel like a child who hasn't grown up.
我突然覺得自己 就是個乳臭未乾的小鬼
It's so beautiful. Do you want to take a look around?
好漂亮 妳要看看這邊嗎
Sure.
好啊
These must be the materials, right?
這些應該是素材吧
This is…
這是…
There's only half left.
只有半邊呢
That's part of the pearl shell.
那是珍珠貝的一部分
Is this the broken part?
這是碎掉才這樣的嗎
No, it's intentionally cut into small pieces for easier processing.
不是 切成小片比較容易加工
Because the shell is hard.
因為貝殼很硬
Is this used for grinding?
這需要用磨的嗎
Yes, but it's hard to grind with sandpaper,
沒錯 但是用磨砂紙很難修磨
so you need to use a diamond file.
所以得用鑽石銼刀
How should I put it?
該怎麼說
I thought it would be similar to the seal carving taught in class.
我還以為會跟上課時學做印章差不多
Can I really do this well?
我真的做得了嗎
Mr. Sajo?
你怎麼了
I'm fine. This is…
沒什麼 這個是...
These are beautiful.
這個很漂亮耶
These are abalone shells transported from New Zealand.
這是從紐西蘭進口的鮑魚殼
Do you like this kind?
你喜歡這種的嗎
Rather than saying I like it…
與其說是喜歡...
Mr. Sajo, would you like to make something?
你要不要親手做點什麼呢
Body touch alert!
肢體接觸警報！
It's a rare opportunity.
既然難得來一趟
If I just buy something and go home, I feel a bit remorseful.
如果只買東西回去好像也說不過去
Great.
太好了
What would you like to make, Miss Sasaki?
笹木小姐 妳想做什麼樣的東西呢
Last time, I made a bracelet by stringing small shells together,
上次我把小貝殼串成了手鏈
so this time I want to make a necklace.
這次我想做條項鏈
That's a good idea.
這主意不錯
What about you, Mr. Sajo?
佐城先生你呢
Let me think.
讓我想想...
Right now, I only have a vague idea.
我現在腦海裡只有個雛形
In that case, it is best to first consider what you want to make.
這樣我建議你還是先想好要做什麼
If you accidentally wear out the shell, it would be a problem.
要是先切完或磨完貝殼 之後想改就很麻煩了
I see.
這樣啊
That makes sense.
有道理
After all, this is a gift for Natsukawa.
畢竟這是要給夏川的禮物
I want to make something that matches her as much as possible.
我想盡量做個適合她的東西
I'm sorry if I got the wrong idea, but are you giving this as a gift?
希望我沒有會錯意 請問你是打算要送人的嗎
Since you are thinking seriously, I assumed you would give it away.
因為看你思考地那麼認真 我才想說有可能是要送人的
Is that so?
是這樣嗎
Sort of. The birthday of someone I know is coming up.
算是吧 我有個朋友生日快到了
-Is she a female? -Is she a girl?
-是異性朋友嗎 -對方是女生嗎
Yes, I do want to make jewelry or other pretty things.
是的 所以我想做個首飾或漂亮的飾品
Typical of a boy.
不愧是男生
That's a very boyish thought.
很男生的想法
If you want to make it yourself, you should start with these materials.
如果要動手製作的話 就要從這裡面挑選素材
Do you have anything you like?
有看到喜歡的嗎
I'll choose this! It's so cute.
我選這個 這好可愛
A baby shell, huh.
這是貝殼的幼體
Pink? It seems to match Natsukawa quite well.
粉紅色...感覺跟夏川也頗搭的
No, pink won't work, I'll be overwhelmed by its cuteness.
不行 我會被粉紅色萌死
And it's a bit inconsistent with the impression that Natsukawa gives.
而且跟夏川給人的印象有點不符
What's something that can further highlight Natsukawa's strengths?
有什麼能夠襯托出夏川的優點呢
Could it be the person you like?
莫非對方是你喜歡的人嗎
That person who's about to celebrate her birthday.
你那位生日快到的朋友
I really can't hide anything from you.
真是瞞不過妳的眼睛耶
Your girlfriend will be delighted to
你女朋友一定會很高興的
receive handcrafted jewelry for her birthday.
生日禮物是手工製作的首飾
No, she's not my girlfriend.
她不是我女朋友
I have no intention to date her.
我沒有想跟她在一起
Even though I do like her, but it's just my unrequited love.
我是喜歡她沒錯 但這只是我的單戀
I see.
這樣啊...
But if you don't want to date her, why still…?
可是既然你不想跟她在一起 為什麼還要送禮呢
My love story hasn't ended.
我的單戀本身並沒有結束
Because I can't let go of my feelings for her…
因為我還無法割捨對她的感情...
Don't follow me.
你不准跟過來
I fallen for Natsukawa and got rejected by her.
我喜歡上了夏川 然後被她拒絕
Maybe I can't get any further with her.
或許我已經沒辦法再接近她了
Even so,
話雖如此
these two and a half years have not been without gains.
這兩年半來我也並非一無所獲
My studies have improved.
我的功課也變好了
If I hadn't fallen for Natsukawa,
如果我沒有喜歡上夏川
I probably wouldn't have "pushed myself" like this.
我一定不會這樣鞭策自己
So it's my self-satisfaction.
所以這完全是為了滿足我自己
Her birthday is an excuse for me to give her a gift.
生日是我能送禮物給她的藉口
If I can make her smile,
如果她能夠展現笑容的話
it would be my greatest fortune.
我就夠幸運了
There's no one in the world who wouldn't be happy to receive a gift.
這世上沒有人收到禮物會不開心的吧
Really?
是嗎
Yes, that's what I believe.
嗯 我是這麼認為的
Sorry to interrupt, have you made your decision yet?
抱歉打斷你們 你決定好了嗎
Sorry, not yet.
對不起 還沒...
No, I just need to give Natsukawa the gift that I think suits her.
不對 我只要送給夏川 我認為適合她的禮物就好了
Even if she doesn't like it, it doesn't matter.
就算她不喜歡也罷
What's important is that I can give Natsukawa the gift.
重要的是我可以送夏川禮物
Do you have anything lighter colors than the one just now?
請問有比剛才那個更淡一點的顏色嗎
(Dreaming Boy is a Realist, The)
《滿懷美夢的少年是現實主義者》
Airi, catch the ball!
小愛莉 接球
I caught it!
我接到了
Great! Next, let's see who can get to the sea faster!
好 現在看誰比較快跑到海裡
You did great, Airi.
小愛莉妳很棒哦
Very good, very good.
好厲害
Whew, I'm exhausted.
呼 累死我了
Sorry, but you rarely get a break from your club activities.
對不起啊 明明妳的社團活動難得放假
No problem, I like to be active.
我就是喜歡活動身體嘛
Aika, you should take a break. You've been taking care of everything non-stop.
小愛妳才該休息一下 一直寸步不離地照顧妹妹
What a fashionable store.
好時髦的店哦
Does it say "handicraft shop" on the sign?
上面好像寫著手工藝品店耶
Should we make something as a memento?
我們要不要做點東西留作紀念？
I'm going to do it!
我要
Let's go take a look.
我們過去看看吧
I want to make jewelry with this impression.
我想製作這種感覺的飾品
Miss Sasaki, do you have a younger sister?
笹木小姐妳還有妹妹嗎
That was taken when I came here with my father before.
那是之前跟我爸來的時候照的
Miss Sasaki, could it be that you're interested in cosplay?
莫非妳的興趣是角色扮演嗎
Mr. Sajo, you're quite the joker. That's my junior high school uniform.
佐城先生你還真是愛說笑 那是我的國中制服啦
What?
什麼
Sorry, we don't have any ready-made ones here.
真不好意思啊 我們這裡沒有加工好的東西
It's okay, my request was too capricious.
不會 是我的要求太任性了
What on earth is going on?
這到底是怎麼回事啊
This is the closest color to what you want.
這個應該最接近你想要的顏色吧
I'm going to work on this next, right?
所以接下來要加工這個東西
What a beautiful color.
顏色好漂亮
Right now, I'm cutting a hard abalone shell.
現在我正在切割堅硬的鮑魚貝殼
No, that's not the point.
不對 這不是重點
Keep going.
加油 加油
How could this be a junior high school girl!
她這樣怎麼可能是國中生啊
-Look this up. -Mr. Sajo, you're fired up!
-看我的厲害 -佐城先生真是熱血沸騰
I can't help but be fired up.
我不得不沸騰啊
Because I don't know
因為我不知道
who to talk to about my doubts!
該向誰傾訴我心中的疑惑啊
I am Sasaki Fukka, from the third grade at White Beach Junior High School.
我是美白濱女子國中三年級的 笹木風香
Huh? Could this be my first formal introduction?
咦 難道我之前 都沒正式跟你自我介紹過嗎
Uh. Indeed, you surprised me.
呃 是的 我很驚訝
I thought you'd be older.
我還以為妳年紀更大一點
No way, haven't I already told you?
討厭 我就跟你說了嘛
I was just a child not long ago.
我前不久還是個小孩子啊
But, compared to you,
我可能就只是個小孩...
Keep going, keep going, keep going.
加油加油 加加油
Middle school girls are quite something these days.
最近的國中女生真不簡單
I am sorry for keeping you waiting, Miss Sasaki.
笹木小姐 抱歉讓妳久等了
I didn't expect it to be this tough.
我沒想到會這麼困難
It's okay, I'm also having fun.
沒關係 我也很開心
An angel.
妳是天使....
Um, Mr. Sajo?
那個 佐城先生...
Yes!
是
About the topic just now, you really…
關於剛才的話題 你果然...
What's wrong?
怎麼了嗎
You've already given up on that girl, haven't you, Mr. Sajo?
你已經放棄那個女生了對吧
Um, yes.
嗯 是啊
You've already given up on her, why can you still work so hard for her?
明明你已經放棄了 為什麼卻能為了她這麼努力呢
It is indeed puzzling.
妳說得沒錯
The magic is that I can muster the energy if I think it is for her.
但很神奇的是 一想到是為了她 我就能充滿幹勁
No, it's nothing. If you were in love, you'd understand, right?
啊不是 妳也談個戀愛的話 可能就會懂了吧
To be in love?
我...我去談戀愛嗎
Excuse me, but what's in love?
請問...什麼是戀愛？
Personally, I doubt it will be a pleasant experience.
就我個人經驗來說 可能不是多麼愉快的一件事
Is that so?
是嗎
Uh-huh, I'm the one more interested in what love is.
嗯 我自己才想知道什麼是戀愛呢
I have been looking for this answer for two and a half years and haven't found it.
我尋找了兩年半 仍然找不到答案
-What's wrong? -Nothing.
-怎麼了嗎 -沒事
After hearing my words,
聽了我的故事
do you feel like it's better not to be in love?
妳是不是覺得不如別談戀愛？
No, not at all.
我...才沒有
Even though it was unrequited love, it wasn't just bitter memories.
雖然我是單戀 但也不是只有辛酸的回憶
If it weren't for this love,
如果沒有這份戀情
I would probably be more childish now.
我現在應該會更加幼稚吧
I see.
這樣啊...
Hello there.
妳好
-Huh? -My apologies.
-咦 -不好意思
Today's craft class has ended.
今天的手工課程已經結束了
Oh, really? That's a shame.
哎呀 是嗎 真可惜
Did you hear that, Airi?
小愛莉妳聽到了吧
We'll come again next time.
我們下次再來吧
Thank you for that, feel free to look around.
謝謝 歡迎妳們隨便看看
Wow, how cute! So it can actually make something like this?
哇 好可愛 居然做得出這種東西
So beautiful.
好漂亮哦
C-Can we start eating yet?
我還不能開動嗎
Wait a bit longer, okay?
我們再等一下好不好？
It can't be him, can it?
不可能是他吧
Aika, here you go.
來囉 小愛
Thank you.
謝謝
Airi wants some too!
愛莉也要
What I'm giving to Airi is
小愛莉妳的是...
a special kid's meal!
兒童特別餐
Great, that's fantastic. Kei, what about you?
好棒哦 太好了呢愛莉 圭妳吃什麼呢
A super-special deluxe tropical meal.
超級特別熱帶豪華套餐
Just kidding. Let's eat together.
騙妳的啦 我們一起吃吧
It's so cold.
好冰哦
There's also pineapple. Airi, do you want some?
這裡還有鳳梨 小愛莉妳要吃嗎
I want some!
我要吃
Aika, what's wrong?
小愛妳怎麼了
Nothing. I think I just saw someone who looks like him.
沒什麼 剛才我好像看到跟他很像的人...
We went out of our way to invite Sajo,
我們明明特地去找了小佐城
but he was not home today. He is passing up an opportunity.
他偏偏今天不在家 真是虧大了
Did he really go to work?
他真的是去打工嗎
Or maybe he went on a date?
該不會是去約會了
Anyone could, but not him!
他那個人怎麼可能啊...
After all, Sajo's got his heart set on you.
畢竟小佐城對妳一心一意嘛
That is…
那是…
Sister…
姊姊
Oh dear.
哎呀
Come to sister. It's okay, it's okay.
有姊姊在 沒事的
Mr. Sajo, your accessories haven't been completed yet.
你的飾品沒能來得及完成...
I'm sorry.
對不起
No need to apologize.
妳不用道歉啦
I can't keep you wandering around until it's late.
我可不能帶著妳遊蕩到太晚
If I didn't have a curfew…
要是我沒有門禁就好了
No, no, no, your father would worry.
不不不 妳爸爸會擔心的
We must come again next time.
下次我們一定還要再來哦
I'll make one for you then.
嗯 到時候我就做一個禮物給妳
Really?
真的嗎
Yeah. And also…
嗯 還有...
I'll give you a safety alarm to use on your way to school.
我要送妳一個 上學途中用的防狼警報器
Will…
我…
Will I be in a relationship when I go to high school?
我上了高中也會談戀愛嗎
I imagined it and started to get a little scared.
想像了一下後 讓我有點害怕...
What are you laughing at!
你笑什麼啦
Sorry, don't worry.
抱歉 妳不用擔心啦
Because there is simply no time to be afraid.
因為根本沒有時間讓妳害怕
Is that so?
是這樣嗎
You can look forward to it.
妳就敬請期待吧
Even if you're a senior, you're too composed.
你這個學長也太故作從容了
Just caring about the timing is meaningless.
光是在意時機也沒有意義
Love always comes unexpectedly. You can never plan for it.
戀愛都是突如其來的 只會讓人措手不及
The next stop is Wakamatsu. Wakamatsu.
下一站 若松
You must be tired. I'll wake you up when we arrive.
妳累了吧 到站我會叫妳起來
Maybe…
說不定...
N-Nothing.
沒...什麼
She does have a middle schooler's side.
她也還是有國中生的一面嘛
YOU HAVE BEEN INVITED TO A GROUP CHAT
(群組邀請)
What's up?
這是什麼...
DARE TO REFUSE OUR INVITATION. YOU'RE REALLY HIGH UP, AREN'T YOU? You're really high up, aren't you?
(竟敢拒絕我們的邀約) 你真是高高在上啊
Huh? What is this?
天哪 這是什麼
Why is she wearing a swimsuit? And this is White Beach, right?
為什麼她穿著泳裝 而且這裡是美白濱吧
Mr. Sajo…
佐城先生...
No way.
不會吧...